tech2connect.com 2010-12-23

# Terms and Privacy Policy for Design SEO Services at Tech2connect.com

The privacy of our visitors to Tech2connect.com is important to us. we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit Tech2connect.com, and how we convoy your information with respect. 

We never sell your personal information to third parties. We collect your contact information to conduct business with you. We also use third party advertisements on tech2connect.com (like Livezilla) to support our site. but we do not save any critical information in cookies. We use latest W3C valid technology to present our information. Tech2connect.com is a freelance web design service provider directed to general public. We do not collect any information form Children. If any Child use any personal information, his or her parent may contact to support [at]tech2connect.com to remove that record. We do not ask for Date of birth of a customer but children are not allow to order for any web design services. 

The privacy of our visitors to Tech2connect.com is important to us. we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit Tech2connect.com, and how we convoy your information with respect. 

We never sell your personal information to third parties. We collect your contact information to conduct business with you. We also use third party advertisements on tech2connect.com (like Livezilla) to support our site. but we do not save any critical information in cookies. We use latest W3C valid technology to present our information. Tech2connect.com is a freelance web design service provider directed to general public. We do not collect any information form Children. If any Child use any personal information, his or her parent may contact to support [at]tech2connect.com to remove that record. We do not ask for Date of birth of a customer but children are not allow to order for any web design services.
